Tree Fruit Research Center, Wenatchee Records 1924-1973
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Tree Fruit Research Center, Wenatchee Records
1924-1973
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
University Archives 190
560 folders 11 linear feet 11 containers
Collection contains correspondence, office files, project and research files, publications and papers from individuals within the center, etc.
Organizational History:
The Tree Fruit Research Center was officially established in 1938 by an act of the State Legislature, but the initiatory step occurred in 1926 when the fruit growers of the Wenatchee district sent a committee to WSC to make a plea that the State College Agriculture Experiment Station carry on more effective experiments in the Wenatchee area. Fred Overley was the first superintendent and came to be regarded as the father of the center. Other records of the Tree Fruit Experiment Station are found in University Archives 77.
This collection contains materials from 1927 to 1973. The materials are roughly divided into the following categories: research projects with which the center was involved, reports of research, publications and papers papers of various individuals within the center, correspondence and other office files pertaining the development of the center, its personnel and research, etc. The materials are arranged by these categories except the office files which are arranged alphabetically.
The Collection is open for research use.
Archives 190: Tree Fruit Research Center Records of the Washington State University Tree Fruit Research Center at Wenatchee were accessioned by the University Libraries in 1978 (UA78-18).
Lindner, Robert C.--Archives; Overley, Fred Lloyd, 1884---Archives
Washington State University. Tree Fruit Research Center, Wenatchee--Archives; Washington State University. Tree Fruit Research Center, Wenatchee--Records and correspondence
Agricultural experiment stations--Washington (State)--Wenatchee--Archives; Agricultural extension work--Research--Washington (State)--Archives; Fruit--Diseases and pests--Research--Washington (State)--Archives; Fruit trade--Research--Washington (State)--Archives
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities; Agriculture
- Office files pertaining to the development of the Center, research, and personnel (Alphabeticaly arranged)
  - Agreements and contracts-Public Utility District, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agreements between Mrs. Barbara Mihelich, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agreements-Washington State Wheat Commission, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Society for Horticultural Science, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ASHS, 1972, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ALCOA, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Area Development Administration, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bills of sale, 195-61 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boundary of experiment station property, 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buildings, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and land-College Farm and Branch Exp. Stations, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and land-Robinson Land Purchase Corporation, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Building program-Entomology Building, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Building project letters, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CA storage and misc., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Campell vs. Chevron Chemical, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Capital outlay and priority, 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Census, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Certificates, patronage dividents, 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Charcoal, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chemical Thinning Radio Service, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chelan County-Overall econ. development program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chrysanthemum project records, etc., 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Construction-Pending, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Container research- USDA and WSC cooperative project, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Deer damage, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Deer repellant project, 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Re. Degman position, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Dept. of Hort.-Active projects, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Director's memo, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Effect of high water tables and flooding on fruit trees, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Equipment owned by TFES, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Equipment of specifications, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Equal employment opportunity employer info. report, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Faculty committee reports, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Fielmen list, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Finally revised exp. station programs for the Division of Hort., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Finance-primarily related to history preceding establishment of Tree Fruit Research Commission, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Foreign correspondence, foreign itinerary, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Fruit marketing agreements, 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Grant applications, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Helping Korean Orphan-Choon Hee Yoon, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - History of the apple, etc., 1924-1945 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Import permit, 1956-1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Indirect costs on grants, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Industrial Insurance claims, 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Interregional Technical Committee, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Landscaping, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Re. R. C. Lindner memorial fund, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Memos re. labor unions, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Memos to staff members, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Memos to staff members, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Memos re. travel authorization, 1969, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Memos re. time card wage scales, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Memo of understanding of Wash. Agricultral Exp. Station with the Bureau of Plant Industry (USDA), with Research Scholarship Foundation of the Wash. State Hort. Assoc. and with Columbia View Exp. Plots (USDA Tree Fruit Branch), 1947-1964 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Minority employment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Minutes of meeting of the Herbicide Council, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Minutes of superintendents' meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Misc. Import papers, 1950-1965 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - National Agric. Library, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - New Building, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Notes of establishment-Wenatchee Esp. Station, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Orchard growing cost (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Overley, F. L. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Overley Lab dedication, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Overley Memorial fund correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
  - Overtime work authorization, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Payment-Janie M. Critchell, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Personnel-Misc., 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Personnel-Homer Coolfe, Asst. in Entomology, 1951-1957 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Personnel-Phyllis Ratzsch, 1957-1964 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Personnel-George Weeks, 1948-1951 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Personnel-J. West, 1943-1967 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Personnel-Richard E. Welton, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Personnel-Susan Whaley, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Personnel-Josef Wieneke, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Personnel-Richard E. Woodruff, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Personnel-Ted Wright, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - President E. O. Holland, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Pesticide regulations, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Plant introduction, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Programs, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Promotional examination announcements, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Property inventory, 1938-1961 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - (US) Public Health Toxicology Lab., 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Publications on standing order and list of professional journals, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Quotations, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Research policy, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Research grant in aid, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Research proposal to NSF, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Research and scholarship foundation of Wash. State Hort Assoc.--Real Estate Contract, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Reservation of rooms, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Spray records complied by Jim Eakin ,and fertilizer records, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - State Health Dept., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Statistics and information for central committee meetings, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Study Council, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Superintendents' memos to staff members, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Technical action panel -- Chelan-Douglas county, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - TFRC--Staff list and misc. (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - TFRC--Songs, poems and others, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Tree survey, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Variety list, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Visitors to the station, 1935-1953 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Visit of Legislative Budget Committee, Oct. 1957 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Voucher approval-Western Bakery, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Wash. Apple Commission, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Wash. Dept. of Agric.--Tree certification, inspection, 1964, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Water sample reports, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Western Avenue Orchards, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Winter injury report, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - WSU faculty nanual, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Research Projects
  - Project 704-Horticulture, 1944-1954 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - 497-Horticulture (varietal investigations), 1944-1956 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Project Correspondence, 1945-1951 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Project 404-Soil science, 1946-1954 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Project progress report-general, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Project 849-Entomology, 1947-1951 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Project 472-Hort., 1947-1951 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Project 773-Chemistry, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Project 640-Hort., 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Project 244-Hort., 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Project 460-Soil science, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Project 903-Soil science, 1947-1954 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Project 536-Hort., 1947-1957 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Project 944-Plant pathology, 1948-1954 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Project progress report-Hort., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Project progress report-Hort., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Project 1030-Hort., 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Project 879-Hort., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Project 552-Soil science, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Project 171, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Project 495-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Project 705-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Project 426-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Project 245-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Project 563-Entom., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Project 600-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Project 1026-Plant pathology, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Project 909-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Air Purification, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Project 880-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Project 524-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Project 797-Hort., 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Project 791-Entom., 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Project 1011-Soil Science, 1951-1953 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Project 451-Plant pathology, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Project 1042-Plant pathology, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Project 751-Soil science, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Project 738-Hort., 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Project 503-Handling and storage of fruits, 1951-1959 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Project 449-Plant pathology, 1951-1960 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Project 1103-Agronomy, 1951-1960 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Project 335-Hort., (USDA-WSC research projects), 1951-1960 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Project 796-Snow mold (Wm. R. Fischer's project, formerly Roderick Sprague's project), 1951-1961 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Project progress reports--fruit washing trials, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Project W-6, New Plants, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Apple juice studies, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Bartlett pear experimental plot, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Projects correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Project 1169-Entom., 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Old proposed projects, 1952-1959 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Project 590-Plant pathology, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Red Bartlett project, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - New project-Premature, uneven ripening of peaches, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Project 1244-Plant pathology, 1955-1958 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Project 1299-Dept. of Hort., E. S. Degman in charge, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Project 1187-Entom., 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Project 604-1956 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Apple varieties, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Project 1337-Pear decline, 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Project 1417-L. P. Batjer, effect of pesticides and plant growth substances on tree foliage and fruit, 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Project 1504-Harvesting and handling apples in bulk bins, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Project 1505-Storage of apples and pears, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Lindner's project 1638-Mutagens from plant sources as antiviral agents, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Project 1419-Bee poisoning, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Lindner's project 1699-Indentification and mech. of action of pear psylla toxin., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - WSU project 805- revised, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Cherry cracking papers, (R. M. Bullock) (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Project 999-Pectic substances (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Project 1152-Hort. processing (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of frost fruit service, Okanogan, WA, season, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Weather Bureau-Report on fruit frost work in Chelan Douglas and Grant, Springs, 1931, 1932, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of frost fruit service, Okanogan, WA, season, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of fruit-frost service, Wenatchee, WA, season, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Annual report of fruit-frost service, Okanogan, season, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Frost protection in the Wenatchee district (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecast and fruit-frost investigations, Okanogan, season, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of fruit-frost service, Wenatchee, season, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecast and fruit-frost investigation, Wenatchee District, season, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecast and fruit-frost investigation, Okanogan District, season, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of fruit-frost service in Wenatchee District, season, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecast and fruit-frost investigation, Okanogan District, season, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Research data-Photosnthesis data, (Cornell Univ.) (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Blossoming data, 1941-1963 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Blossoming data, 1941-1963 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - USDA Weather Burea-Annual report of fruit-frost service in Wenatchee, 1942 season (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecast and fruit-frost investigation, Wentachee District, season, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - USDA Weather Bureau-Annual report of fruit-frost and forecast investigation, Wenatchee District, 1944 season (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Memo of understanding on virus studies, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Research Initiative 171, 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - Naval research, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 203-204)
  - Project 171 reports, 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Pear decline, Mt. Adams, 1952-1962 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Federal funds, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Maturity data, 1954-1964 (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Pear decline, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Project # 865 revision, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Research data-Purines, etc., 1959-1962 (Box 4, Folder 211)
  - Pear decline, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - General weather, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - Pear Psylla Toxin, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - Pear decline, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Psylla toxin data, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - Stem-Pitting, (Golden delicious decline), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 217)
  - Kinetin, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 218)
  - Thirty year temperature means, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - Psylla partition, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 220)
  - Psylla toxin, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 221)
  - Pear viruses, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 222)
  - Brandy, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 223)
  - Research papers on pear decline (Box 4, Folder 224)
  - Pear decline, (Lindner) (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - Apple stocks and varieties, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - Stem-end Resselt of Goldens, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - Prosser pear decline, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - Starling control, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - Stony-pit, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Research project 1834-interferon-like antiviral mechanism, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Soil problems in Manson area, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecasts and fruit-frost surveys, Wenatchee, seasons, 1945-1952 (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Annual report of minimum temperature forecasts and fruit-frost surveys, Okanogan, seasons, 1945-1951 (Box 5, Folder 234)
  - Annual report (1954-56)-equipment for production, harvesting, and orchard handlings of tree fruits (Box 5, Folder 235)
  - Annual report (1956-58)-equipment for production, harvesting, and orchard handling of tree fruits (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Annual report (1958-59)- fruit harvesting and handling studies, Wenatchee, Project AE c3-9 and AE c3-10 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Annual report (1959-61)-fruit harvesting, and handling studies, Wenatchee, Projects AE c3-9 and AE c3-10 (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - Annual report (1961-62)-fruit harvesting, and handling studies, Wenatchee, Projects AE c3-9 and AE c3-10 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - Annual report (1962-63)-fruit harvesting and handling studies, Wenatchee, Projects AE c3-9 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - Reports of the Western Cooperative Oil Spray Project, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - Reports of the WCOSP, 1928-1941 (Box 5, Folder 242-258)
  - Reports of the WCOSP, 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 259-275)
  - Papers-Burts Everett (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Papers-Ted Anthon (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - Papers-Max W. Williams (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - Papers and resume-R. P. Covey (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - Papers-J. J. McRitchie (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - Papers-Eakin Ko (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Publications and papers-R. Paul Larsen, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - Papers-Bill Chennault, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - Publications and papers-Del Ketchie, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - Publications and papers-Stanley Hoyt, up to, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Publications-Hugh C. Kirkpatrick, up to, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - Publications-Roderick Sprague, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - Papers-Nels Benson (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Publications-Nels Benson (Box 7, Folder 289-290)
  - R. C. Lindner (1914-68)'s life story by Kirkpatrick (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Request for Lindner's article "Chemical Tests in the Diagnosis of Plant Virus Disease" in the Botanical Review, 1961, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Requests for Lindner's paper, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - (RNA) requests for Lindner's paper reprints, 1956-1964 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Requests for BIDS and Price Quotations, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Requests for Lindner's reprints, 1955-1960 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Lindner's publication list, 1934-1965 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Lindner's publications (reprints) (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Lindner correspondence A-B, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Lindner correspondence with Agric. Extension Service, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Lindner correspondence with Architect Office, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - Lindner correspondence re. annalytical methods, 1942-1962 (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - Lindner correspondence from Nels Benson, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - Lindner memo to budget office, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Lindner correspondence C-Mc, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Lindner correspondence with the Chamber of Commerce, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Lindner correspondence re. color test, 1947-1959 (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Lindner correspondence with Dept. of Entomology, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - Lindner correspondence with Dept. of Agric. Chemistry, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - Lindner correspondence with Dept. of Agric. Engineering, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Lindner correspondence with Dept. of Horticulture, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Lindner correspondence with Dept. of Plant Pathology, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Lindner correspondence with misc. departments, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 313)
  - Lindner correspondence re. German exchange students, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Foreign correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Lindner correspondence re. foreign visitors itinerary, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Lindner correspondence M-W, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Lindner correspondence with National Grape Cooperative Assoc. Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Lindner correspondence with Prosser station, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Lindner correspondence with Public Utility District, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Lindner correspondence-Recommendation letters, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - Lindner correspondence with Research and Scholarship Foundation, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - Lindner correspondence with Staff Personnel Office, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 323)
  - Lindner correspondence with Statistical Services, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 324)
  - Lindner correspondence with S. C. Markley (Building and Grounds), 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - Lindner correspondence re. pear decline (Box 7, Folder 326)
  - Lindner correspondence with Southwestern Wash. E. S. (Vancouver), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 327)
  - Lindner correspondence re. Spectro-method reprints, 1951-1956 (Box 7, Folder 328)
  - Lindner's correspondence re. St!in Test, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - Lindner's correspondence with State Dept. of Health, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - Lindner correspondence with Wash. State Hort. Assoc., 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 331)
  - Lindner corresponence re. surplus property (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - Lindner correspondence re. therapy, 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 333)
  - Lindner correspondence re. trip to Australia, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - Lindner correspondence with USDA various depts., 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Lindner correspondence with USDA-Agric. Engineering Research Division, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - Lindner correspondence with US Public Health, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Lindner correspondence with Wash. Apple Commission, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Lindner correspondence with Western Wash. Exp. Station, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Lindner correspondence with Wenatchee High School "On the Job" training, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - Lindner correspondence with Wenatchee-Wenoka Growers Inc., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - Lindner correspondence with WSU director of research (Box 7, Folder 342)
- Correspondence
  - A-U, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 343-359)
  - with US Dept. of Agric., 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - with USDA Agric. Engineering-S. W. McBirney, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - with US Weather Bureau, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 362)